http://www.oblates.com.au/privacy-policy

Login
This site www.oblates.com.au is owned and administered by the Australian Province of the Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate which is a Not for Profit organisation based at 649 Burke Rd, Camberwell, Australia(ABN: 79 934 022 952 ACN: 004 535 317) and complies with the following:Privacy PolicyThe Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to all Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia Web sites owned and administrated by the Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia and governs data collection and usage. By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationThe Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia collect personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of this Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through public message boards on the site, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia do not read any of your private online communications.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia encourage you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to our sites so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of those directly owned and administered by Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia.Use of your Personal InformationThe Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia collect and use your personal information to operate the Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia Web sites and deliver the services you have requested.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from its affiliates. The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia keep track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within our Website, in order to determine what Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia Web sites use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience.A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia pages, or register with Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia site or services, a cookie helps The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia Web site the information you previously provided can be retrieved so you can easily use the Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia features that you customized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationThe Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia secure the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementThe Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia are protecting your information.Contact InformationThe Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia welcome your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia have not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Missionary Oblates of Mary Immaculate Australia at omi_website@oblates.com.au.
Search
Provincial contactProvincial Administration: PO. Box 384 (649 Burke Rd)Camberwell Vic 3124  Ph   (03) 9805 8800Fax  (03) 9813 2696
